https://www.gopopup.com/en/page/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Data Owner: POP CORNER NETWORK, S.L.
Tax Id: ESB65735136
Address: Carrer Sardenya, 229, 4º - 08013 Barcelona (Spain)
Commercial Registry: Tomo 43027, Folio 78, Hoja B-418398, Inscripción 1.
e-mail: hello[AT]gopopup.com
Telephone number: +34 93 543 64 78
1.- Pursuant to European Regulation 2016/679, General Data Protection (hereinafter, GDPR), you are hereby informed that all personal data you provide to us expressly through the website www.gopopup.com will be included in a file owned by POP CORNER NETWORK, S.L. (hereinafter, Go-PopUp) as the data controller responsible for the processing of personal data.
Under no circumstance will data be disclosed to any third party without your express consent and you will always be informed of the company or companies that will process your data.
Your data will be protected with the technical and organisational measures needed to guarantee the security of personal data and prevent their alteration, loss, unauthorised processing or access, considering the scope, context and purpose of the processing, the state of technology and the existing risks, among other control procedures to secure information systems. Criteria were taken into account when determining these measures such as the scope, context and purposes of processing, the state of technology and the existing risks.
2.- At any time, you may exercise your rights of access, rectification, to object, cancellation, information, to be forgotten, restriction of processing and the portability of your data processed, by sending a letter indicating the right exercised to the mailing address indicated above or to the following email address: hello@gopopup.com.
3.- To exercise the rights mentioned in the foregoing section, you must indicate your personal data to us (first name, surnames, mailing address, telephone number, email address and any other data we may use to verify your identity and contact you) along with a copy of your identity card or equivalent documentation. All communications with you will be handled with absolute confidentiality. All of your personal data will be processed with due diligence in accordance with the provisions of Spanish law; without prejudice to the above, if you decide to publish any public information or message on the WEBSITE, the publication will be managed in accordance with your request.
4.- Pursuant to article 24 of the new European Regulation, Go—PopUp, as the data controller has implemented all the necessary security measures to guarantee the security of the personal data in accordance with the state of technology and regularly checks, evaluates and assesses the efficacy of the technical and organisational measures aimed at guaranteeing processing security.
5.- For the exclusive purpose of providing the services contracted through the WEBSITE, Go—PopUp may process personal data owned by the CLIENT in which case it will access them as the data controller under the scope of the provisions of the new European Regulation.
6.- Our services may possibly use cookies to provide you with a better experience when using the WEBSITE. Cookies are small storage devices that are installed on your computer hard drive to optimise our services. You may modify or block the cookies at any time although your experience may be affected in such case. Please read the cookie policy for more information.
7.- All of the data relating to payment methods will be processed confidentially in compliance with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) rules by suppliers contracted by Go—PopUp for this purpose. Go—PopUp will not use the data corresponding to your payment methods either directly or through suppliers that comply with the security measures established in the PCI regulations to carry out transactions other than those expressly requested by you.
8.- Pursuant to the provisions of the terms and conditions of use and contracting, Go—PopUp will provide each of the parties to the Transactions with data provided by the other party in order to allow compliance with their respective obligations, which are personal data expressly assigned by you for the purpose established upon assignment. The recipient of the data will receive them as the data processor and, as such, undertakes to process them in compliance with all of the security measures established by current personal data protection laws and delete them as soon as the contractual relationship with the other party ends, always in compliance with said law.
9.- When registering for Online Pop-Ups webinar / broadcasting sessions accessible via the page “Online Pop-Ups Shopping Center" (https://www.gopopup.com/en/products/onlinepopupshoppingcenter), the data provided by the website visitor when using the “Join Pop-Up” function; in other words, their name, email address and telephone number, will be used for session notifications and will be shared with the organizer or host of the session for future communications or commercial purposes. Go—PopUp as well as the organizer or host of the session will receive the data as the data processor. As such, they undertake to process all data in accordance with all security measures established by current personal data protection laws and to delete the data as soon as such a request is made by the data subject, always in compliance with the corresponding laws and regulations.
How it works
About Us
References
Career
Press
FAQ's
Permits
Terms & Conditions
Send
We use own and third party cookies to use analysis and measurement of our website to improve our services. If you continue to browse, consider accepting its use. You can change the settings or get more information here."
View cookies policy.
I accept
